Guide to the Bates Worldwide, Inc. Records, 1934-2005 and undated RL.00090
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Client Files Series, 1969-2005 and undated; 136 boxes
  - Carter-Wallace Co.
    - Prophylactics--Trojan condoms
      - Brand overview, 1996
        - Review/creative strategy, 1990-1991 (Box CL49)
        - Sampling opportunities in magazines, outdoor program, GQ, 1991-1992 (Box CL49)
        - Sex in America, overview 1994 (Box CL49)
          Agency review of a major study of American sexual attitudes and habits undertaken by the University of Chicago.
        - Sexually-transmitted diseases (STDs), 1990-1991 (Box CL49)
        - STDs/AIDS, 1991-1995 (Box CL49)
        - Strategy and information for television campaign, 1994-1995 (Box CL49)
        - Taking Trojans into the 1980s, 1985 (Box CL49)
        - Teen research, 1994-1996, Folder 1 of 3 (Box CL49)
        - Teen research, 1994-1996 (continued), Folders 2-3 of 3 (Box CL50)
        - Types of condoms: ultra thin, Baggy, etc., 1990, 1995 (Box CL50)
        - Work sessions, 1993-1995 (Box CL50)
  - CDW
    - Proofs and printed materials, 1999, 2002 (Box CL51)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank
    - Artwork, 1996-1997 (Box CL52)
    - Brochures and flyers, 1996 (Box CL52)
    - Proofs, 1996 (Box CL51)
  - Chemical Bank
    - Artwork, 1994-1995 (Box CL51)
    - Brochures, 1995 (Box CL52)
    - Chromes and sketches, 1994-1996, 4 folders (Box CL52)
  - Cisco Systems
    - Print advertising, 2000 (Box CL51)
  - Citizen Watch
    - Competitive advertising, 1999 (Box CL52)
    - Eco-Drive watch printed materials, 2000 (Box CL52)
  - Cunard Lines
    - Artwork, 1994-1998 (Box CL53-CL55)
      - Disk 49. Logos (Box CL53-CL55)
        Disk contains 1 color and 2 black and white logos for Berlitz #1 Top Rated Ships 1998
    - Proofs, 1994-1998 (Box CL56)
  - Derivion
    - Proofs, 2000, 2 folders (Box CL57)
  - Eastman Kodak
    - Proofs, 2000 (Box CL57)
  - Eveready
    - Correspondence, 2000, 2 folders (Box CL58)
  - Footlocker
    Includes Lady Footlocker, Kids Footlocker.
    - Artwork, 1994-1998, 8 folders (Box CL58)
      - Disk 40. Fonts (Box CL58)
      - Disk 41. Fonts (Box CL58)
      - Disk 42. Fonts (Box CL58)
      - Disk 43. Logos (Box CL58)
        Disk contains two logos entitled NBA, and Allstar Weekend.
      - Disk 44. Logos (Box CL58)
        Disk contains three logos for NBA on TNT.
      - Disk 58. QuarkXPress files (Box CL58)
    - Artwork, 1994-1998 (continued) (Box CL59-CL61)
      - Disk 45. Logos (Box CL59-CL61)
        Disk contains various National Football League and Nike logos.
      - Disk 46. Logos (Box CL59-CL61)
        Disk contains various '97 NFL Experience logos.
      - Disk 47. Photos (Box CL59-CL61)
        Disk contains two black and white photos entitled Mrs. Stern and 3 Beauties.
      - Disk 48. Artwork (Box CL59-CL61)
      - Disk 57. Logos (Box CL59-CL61)
        Disk contains a Nike logo.
    - Proofs, 1995-1998 (Box CL62)
  - Hertz Rent-a-Car
    - Campaigns, 1974-1978, 3 folders (Box CL63)
      Includes One Less Thing to Worry About and O.J. Simpson Superstar campaigns.
    - Proofs, 1974-1979 (Box CL64)
  - Hyundai America
    - General (Box CL65)
      - Advertising planner, 2002
        - Disk 23. Program file (Box CL65)
          Disk contains a program entitled Hyundai 2002 Catalog and supporting files
      - Competitive advertising, 1984 May 2 (Box CL65)
      - Competitive spending-Audi, 1985 Aug. 19 (Box CL65)
      - Dealer associations, 1985 Nov.-1986 Jan. (Box CL65)
      - Los Angeles Angels-KTLA, 1990 (Box CL65)
      - Marketing, 1985-1986, 2 folders (Box CL65)
      - Marlboro group merchandising, 1986 July (Box CL65)
      - Media-print, 1986 (Box CL65)
      - Media-television, 1986, 2 folders (Box CL65)
      - Minnesota Twins, 1990 (Box CL65)
      - New Orleans dealer meeting, 1986 Jan. 31, 2 folders (Box CL66)
      - New York Giants radio, 1988 (Box CL66)
      - New York Mets television, 1991 (Box CL66)
      - News release-- Chair and Speedy campaigns, 2001 (Box CL66)
      - Oakland A's on KICU-TV, 1990 (Box CL66)
      - Owner communications kit, 2002, 2 folders (Box CL66)
      - Pride of Ownership, 2001 Oct. 11 (Box CL66)
      - Production budget review, 1986 June 30 (Box CL66)
      - Prospect target analysis, 2002 Feb., 2 folders (Box CL66)
      - Research, 1985 Oct.-1986 Jan., 2 folders (Box CL66)
      - Sales forecasts, 1986 Oct. (Box CL66)
      - Spring dealer meetings, 1986 Apr. 8 (Box CL66)
      - Volkswagen reports, 1985 (Box CL66)
    - Excel model (Box CL67)
      - 1987 model year television package, 1986 July-Nov., 2 folders (Box CL67)
      - 3 Door Intro, 1986 May 22 (Box CL67)
      - Christmas Present, 1986 Nov. (Box CL67)
      - College pre-production, 1985 Oct. (Box CL67)
      - Common Sense, 1986, 2 folders (Box CL67)
      - Correspondence, 1995 (Box CL67)
      - Event production, 1986 Oct.-Nov. (Box CL67)
      - Media-radio, 1986 Mar. (Box CL67)
      - Pre-production meeting, 1986 Apr. 11 (Box CL67)
      - Product introduction television package, 1986 Aug.-Oct., 2 folders (Box CL67)
      - Running footage, 1985 Dec. (Box CL67)
    - Sonata model, 1997 (Box CL68)
      - Launch kit, 1997 (Box CL68)
      - Newspaper inserts, 1997 (Box CL68)
  - Hoffman-La Roche
    - Saridon case study, 2002 (Box CL69)
  - Imperial Tobacco
    - Billings, 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box CL69)
    - Contracts, 1995-1996 (Box CL69)
  - Joint Recruiting Advertising Program (JRAP)
    - General (Box CL69)
      - Benchmark proposals, 1991, 2 folders (Box CL69)
      - C-1 manpower report, 1992, 2 folders (Box CL69)
      - Correspondence from the Department of Defense (DOD), 1991 Oct.-1992 Apr., 2 folders (Box CL69)
      - Disclosure statement, 1991 Nov. 27 (Box CL69)
      - Financial records (Box CL70)
        - Budget, 1992 Sept.-1993 Jan., 2 folders (Box CL70)
        - Memoranda, 1991 Oct.-1993 Jan., 7 folders (Box CL70)
        - Receipts, 1992 Feb.-1993 Jan., 9 folders (Box CL71)
      - Manpower reports, 1991 Sept.-Dec., 2 folders (Box CL72)
      - Marketing strategies, 1992, 2 folders (Box CL72)
      - Media planning, 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box CL72)
      - Military funeral planning kit, undated
        - Disk 61. Audio (Box CL72)
          Disk contains one untitled audio file
      - Notes, 1993, 2 folders (Box CL72)
      - Proposals, 1992-1993, 7 folders (Box CL73)
      - Quarterly reports, 1993 (Box CL73)
      - Technical proposal, 1991, Folder 1 of 2 (Box CL73)
      - Technical proposal, 1991 (continued), Folder 2 of 2 (Box CL74)
    - Advertising campaigns
      - Active enlisted, undated, 13 folders (Box CL74)
      - G.I. Bill, undated (Box CL74)
      - Olympics, undated (Box CL74)
      - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) scholarship materials, 2001 (Box CL74)
    - Artwork
      - Chromes, undated (Box CL74)
      - Chromes and other artwork, 1980s-1992 and undated (Box CL75-CL81)
        Includes work performed by Grey Advertising.
    - Proofs, 1986-1992 (Box CL82)
  - Kinney Shoe Corporation
    - Artwork, 1996-1997 and undated (Box CL83-CL86)
    - Proofs, 1996-1997 (Box CL87)
  - KPMG
    - Storyboard books, undated (Box CL88)
  - Marconi
    - Brand development booklet, 2000 (Box CL89)
  - Maxell
    - Artwork, 1995-1996 (Box CL89)
    - Proofs, 1995-1997 (Box CL89)
  - Maxrate.com
    - Proofs, 2000 (Box CL89)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art
    - Artwork, 1990 (Box CL90)
    - Proofs, 1990 (Box CL90)
  - Miller Brewing Co.
    - General (Box CL91)
      - Assorted sports marketing folders, undated (Box CL91)
        Empty folders with radio station, sports team logos displayed on covers.
      - Creative sports marketing files, 1989 (Box CL91)
      - Fanstand, 1989 July (Box CL91)
      - Fred Edelstein Show, 1989 (Box CL91)
      - George Perles Show, 1989 (Box CL91)
      - Impact Productions, 1989 Sept. 6 (Box CL91)
      - Industry historical/projections, 1992 (Box CL91)
      - Intersport Chicago, 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box CL91)
      - Joe Thompson Sports Productions, 1979-1982 (Box CL91)
      - Löwenbräu tracking reports (Vincent Falcone), 1981 (Box CL91)
      - Manhattan Cable--sports, 1989 Mar. 15 (Box CL91)
      - Miller Lite storyboards, 1980s (Box CL91)
      - Miller sponsorships since 1979, 1989 (Box CL91)
      - Miller Sports Club, 1990 Feb. (Box CL91)
      - Miller Sports Highlight 1989 (Box CL91)
      - New York--CBS Sports, 1982-1983 (Box CL91)
      - New York sports radio, 1988 (Box CL91)
      - New York--WNEW Sports Update Extra, 1980-1981 (Box CL91)
      - Power Sportsbeat, 1989 Nov. 9 (Box CL91)
      - Sportsbreak, 1988 Apr. (Box CL91)
      - Sports Channel, 1988 Nov. 9 (Box CL91)
      - Sports Final, 1990 (Box CL91)
      - Sports interview proposal, 1989 July (Box CL91)
      - Sports Magazine, 1978-1987, 2 folders (Box CL91)
      - Sportsview, 1989 Aug. 22 (Box CL91)
      - Sports wrap-ups, 1980-1985 (Box CL91)
      - Television, 1989 (Box CL91)
      - This Week in Baseball, WWOR-TV, 1989 Nov. 27 (Box CL91)
      - Timberwolf productions--agency point of view, 1989 Aug. 15 (Box CL91)
      - The Umpires, 1989 Sept. 4 (Box CL92)
      - WBBM Boston: The Beach, 1989 (Box CL92)
      - WIOD-AM Miami, 1990 (Box CL92)
      - WOW Radio, 1989 Nov. 17 (Box CL92)
    - Celebrity sports
      - Best of the Beach, 1990 (Box CL92)
      - Miller (WCAU, WCIX) Beach, 1990 (Box CL92)
    - College sports
      - Clemson Football Show, 1989 (Box CL92)
      - Clemson University Sports Network, 1989, 2 folders (Box CL92)
      - Eastern Michigan University football, golf, 1989 (Box CL92)
      - Husker Highlights, 1990 (Box CL92)
      - March Madness NCAA First Round, 1990 Mar. (Box CL92)
      - Metro Conference Basketball, 1990 Aug. 29 (Box CL92)
      - Mid-American Conference sports, 1989 (Box CL92)
      - NCAA Big Eight pre-season special, 1989 July 11 (Box CL92)
      - NCAA Big Ten Preview, 1990 May 1 (Box CL92)
      - NCAA Slam Dunk, 1989 (Box CL92)
      - NCAA Tournament, Michigan vs. Xavier, 1989 Mar. 15 (Box CL92)
      - PAC-10 Preview, 1989 (Box CL92)
      - Penn State Game Day, 1989 July 27 (Box CL92)
      - Raycom College Football Report, 1989 May 4 (Box CL92)
      - Siena Basketball w/ Mike Dean, 1989 (Box CL92)
      - Southwest, Southeast, Atlantic Coast conferences, 1979-1985 (Box CL92)
      - University of Southern California (USC), 1979-1980 (Box CL92)
      - University of Tennessee, 1981-1982 (Box CL92)
      - WTNH New Haven--UConn Basketball, undated (Box CL92)
    - Professional sports
      - Albany Yankees, 1989 (Box CL92)
      - Atlanta Braves, 1977-1979, 1991, 3 folders (Box CL92)
      - Atlanta Falcons, 1979-1986, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box CL92)
      - Atlanta Hawks, 1977-1986 (Box CL92)
      - Atlanta Hawks television, 1990-1991 (Box CL92)
      - Baltimore Colts, 1978-1984 (Box CL93)
      - Baltimore Orioles, 1978-1993, 3 folders (Box CL93)
      - Boston Bruins, 1984 (Box CL93)
      - Boston Celtics, 1982-1991, 5 folders (Box CL93)
      - Boston Marathon, 1990, 2 folders (Box CL93)
      - Boston Red Sox, 1976-1987, 4 folders (Box CL93)
      - Boston Red Sox/Bruins historical, 1990 (Box CL93)
      - Boston sports, 1989 (Box CL93)
      - Buffalo Bills, 1982, 1985 (Box CL93)
      - California Angels, 1978-1982, 1991, 2 folders (Box CL93)
      - California Mile, 1989 June 14 (Box CL93)
      - Canterbury Downs, 1989 May 5 (Box CL93)
      - Charlotte Hornets Magazine, 1990-1991 (Box CL93)
      - Charlotte Hornets Playbook, 1990-1991 (Box CL93)
      - Chicago Baseball, 1981-1987 (Box CL93)
      - Chicago Bears (Box CL94)
        - General, 1987-1991 (Box CL94)
        - Cable television, 1989 (Box CL94)
        - Chicago Bears Locker Room, 1989 Apr. (Box CL94)
        - Mike Ditka Show, 1989, 2 folders (Box CL94)
      - Chicago Bulls, 1983-1984 (Box CL94)
      - Chicago Cubs, 1976-1987, 1990-1991, 4 folders (Box CL94)
      - Chicago Sports radio, 1989 (Box CL94)
      - Chicago White Sox, 1979-1987, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box CL94)
      - Cincinnati Bengals, 1977-1982, 1989-1991, 2 folders (Box CL94)
      - Cincinnati-- Bob Trumpy Show, 1989 Oct. 26 (Box CL94)
      - Cincinnati radio Sportstalk, 1990 Jan. 17 (Box CL95)
      - Cincinnati Reds
        - General, 1978-1984 (Box CL95)
        - Big Red Machine, 1990 (Box CL95)
        - Radio, 1990 (Box CL95)
        - Specials, 1990 (Box CL95)
      - Cleveland Browns, 1984-1986, 1990, 2 folders (Box CL95)
      - Cleveland Cavaliers, 1983-1991, 1989, 3 folders (Box CL95)
      - Cleveland Indians
        - General, 1978-1985, 1991, 2 folders (Box CL95)
        - Radio, 1990-1991, 3 folders (Box CL95)
        - Sports Channel, 1991 (Box CL95)
      - CoreStates Championship, 1989 May 3 (Box CL95)
      - Dairyland Race Track, undated (Box CL95)
      - Dallas Cowboys (Box CL95)
      - General, 1976-1991, 3 folders (Box CL95)
      - Dallas Cowboys Gameday, 1989 Dec. 24 (Box CL95)
      - Dallas Cowboys Report, 1991
        - Dallas Cowboys Show, 1989 (Box CL95)
        - Dallas Cowboys Special Edition, 1990 Oct. 25 (Box CL95)
        - Dallas Cowboys Updates (WFAA), 1990 (Box CL95)
        - Jimmy Johnson/Drew Person television, 1989 July (Box CL95)
        - Jimmy Johnson Show, 1989-1990, 4 folders (Box CL96)
        - Pre-season, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box CL96)
        - Press conference, 1991 July 3 (Box CL96)
        - Radio proposal, 1990-1991 Apr., 2 folders (Box CL96)
        - Star of the Game, 1990 (Box CL96)
        - Television, 1990 Jan. 11 (Box CL96)
      - Dallas Mavericks, 1983-1986 (Box CL96)
      - Dallas Trophy Show, 1986 June 18 (Box CL96)
      - Denver Broncos
        - General, 1979-1987 (Box CL96)
        - Dan Reeves Show, 1990 (Box CL96)
        - KCNC-TV, 1991 (Box CL96)
        - Pre/post-game shows, 1989, 2 folders (Box CL96)
        - Pre-season, 1988-1991, 3 folders (Box CL96)
        - Sports specials, 1991 (Box CL96)
      - Denver Huddle, 1989 (Box CL96)
      - Denver Nuggets, 1977-1987 (Box CL96)
      - Detroit contingency fund, 1986 (Box CL96)
      - Detroit Lions
        - General, 1978-1979 (Box CL96)
        - Pre-season television, 1990 (Box CL96)
        - Radio, 1990 (Box CL96)
      - Detroit Pistons, 1989 (Box CL96)
      - Detroit-- The Press Box, undated (Box CL96)
      - Detroit Tigers (Box CL97)
        - General, 1978-1988, 2 folders (Box CL97)
        - Radio, 1990 (Box CL97)
      - Golden State Warriors, 1976-1986 (Box CL97)
      - Green Bay Packers
        - General, 1981-1985 (Box CL97)
        - Green Bay Packer Hour, 1991 (Box CL97)
        - Green Bay Packers Show/Lindy Infante, 1990 (Box CL97)
        - Historical, 1990 Apr. 26 (Box CL97)
        - Radio, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box CL97)
        - Television
          - General, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box CL97)
          - WBAY-TV, 1990 Jan. 26 (Box CL97)
          - WGAB, 1990-1991 (Box CL97)
      - Houston Astros
        - General, 1976-1989, 3 folders (Box CL97)
        - Hispanic, 1991 (Box CL97)
      - Houston Oilers
        - General, 1979-1987 (Box CL97)
        - Houston Oilers Radio Network, 1990 (Box CL97)
        - Houston Oilers vs. Pittsburgh Steelers, 1990 June 15 (Box CL97)
        - Pre-season, 1989-1991, 2 folders (Box CL97)
        - Quarterback Corner with Warren Moon, 1989-1992, 3 folders (Box CL97)
        - Radio, 1991 May 15 (Box CL97)
      - Houston Rockets (Box CL98)
        - General, 1982-1992 (Box CL98)
        - Houston Rockets Coach Show, 1990 (Box CL98)
      - Indiana Pacers, 1983-1990, 2 folders (Box CL98)
      - Indianapolis 500, 1989 Mar. 13 (Box CL98)
      - Indianapolis Colts
        - Lindy Infante Show, 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box CL98)
        - Pre-season television, 1991 (Box CL98)
        - Radio, 1991, 2 folders (Box CL98)
      - Kansas City Chiefs
        - General, 1979 (Box CL98)
        - Marty Schottenheimer Show, 1990 Apr. 6 (Box CL98)
        - Monthly specials, 1990 (Box CL98)
        - Pre-season, 1991 (Box CL98)
      - Kansas City Kings, 1976-1985 (Box CL98)
      - Kansas City Royals, 1978-1986 (Box CL98)
      - Kentucky Derby, 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box CL98)
      - Los Angeles Clippers, 1990-1991 (Box CL98)
      - Los Angeles Dodgers
        - General, 1979-1987 (Box CL98)
        - Radio, 1991 (Box CL98)
      - Los Angeles Lakers (Box CL99)
        - General, 1981-1986, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box CL99)
        - Kareem Abdul-Jabaar, 1989, 2 folders (Box CL99)
      - Los Angeles Lakers, Kings additional, 1987-1989 (Box CL99)
      - Los Angeles Marathon, 1990 (Box CL99)
      - Los Angeles Raiders radio, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box CL99)
      - Los Angeles Rams
        - General, 1978-1980 (Box CL99)
        - John Robinson Show, 1990 July 19 (Box CL99)
        - Radio, 1991, 2 folders (Box CL99)
      - Major League Baseball (MLB) post acetates, 1989-1990 (Box CL99)
      - Mason-Dixon Steeplechase, 1990 (Box CL99)
      - Miami Dolphins
        - General, 1978-1984 (Box CL99)
        - Dan Marino On WTVJ, 1989 July 5 (Box CL99)
        - Radio, 1991 (Box CL99)
      - Miami Heat
        - Billy Thompson Show, 1989 Dec. 4 (Box CL99)
        - Ron Rothstein Radio Show, 1989 Aug. (Box CL99)
      - Milwaukee Brewers
        - General, 1978-1981, 1988-1991, 3 folders (Box CL99)
        - Special, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box CL99)
        - Television, radio, signage, promotions, 1994 Dec. 20 (Box CL99)
      - Milwaukee Bucks, 1977-1986, 2 folders (Box CL99)
      - Minnesota North Stars, 1980-1984 (Box CL99)
      - Minnesota Timberwolves, 1989-1991 (Box CL99)
      - Minnesota Twins, 1978-1987 (Box CL100)
      - Minnesota Vikings
        - General, 1981-1985 (Box CL100)
        - Radio, 1989 (Box CL100)
      - National Basketball Association (NBA)
        - All-Star post-game Miami, 1990 Feb. 11 (Box CL100)
        - Draft Party-Sunshine, 1990 June (Box CL100)
        - Financial analysis acetates, 1989-1990 (Box CL100)
        - NBA/MLB delivery value acetates, 1989-1990 (Box CL100)
        - Post analysis acetates, 1989-1990 (Box CL100)
      - National Football League (NFL)
        - Draft show on WGN-A, 1989 (Box CL100)
        - Films, 1979 (Box CL100)
      - National Hockey League (NHL)
        - Draft, 1989 (Box CL100)
        - Post acetates, 1989-1990 (Box CL100)
      - New England Patriots, 1977-1989 (Box CL100)
      - New Jersey Nets, 1980-1987 (Box CL100)
      - New Orleans Saints
        - General, 1977-1989 (Box CL100)
        - Jim Mora Show, 1991 June 18 (Box CL100)
        - New Orleans Saints Sideline, 1989-1991, 2 folders (Box CL100)
        - Pre-season television, 1988 (Box CL100)
      - New York Giants
        - General, 1976-1986 (Box CL100)
        - Radio, 1989 (Box CL100)
      - New York Islanders, 1979 (Box CL100)
      - New York Jets, 1981-1991, 2 folders (Box CL100)
      - New York Knicks, 1979-1984 (Box CL100)
      - New York Mets, 1978-1987 (Box CL100)
      - New York Rangers, 1976-1983 (Box CL100)
      - New York Yankees
        - General, 1976-1985, Folder 1 of 2 (Box CL100)
        - General, 1976-1985 (continued), Folder 2 of 2 (Box CL101)
        - WABC pre-game show, 1989 (Box CL101)
      - Oakland A's
        - General, 1978-1984, 1990, 2 folders (Box CL101)
        - Hispanic, 1991 (Box CL101)
      - Oakland Raiders, 1977-1984, 2 folders (Box CL101)
      - Orlando Magic, 1991 (Box CL101)
      - Philadelphia 76ers, 1982-1988 (Box CL101)
      - Philadelphia Distance Run, 1989 (Box CL101)
      - Philadelphia Eagles
        - General, 1978-1986 (Box CL101)
        - Buddy Ryan Show, 1986-1990, 5 folders (Box CL101)
        - Eagles Cheers, 1989 Aug. 16 (Box CL101)
        - Radio, 1990 (Box CL101)
      - Philadelphia Flyers, 1981-1985 (Box CL101)
      - Philadelphia Phillies
        - General, 1978-1982 (Box CL101)
        - Cable, 1991 (Box CL101)
      - Philadelphia sports opportunities, 1991 June 19 (Box CL101)
      - Phoenix Cardinals--television, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box CL101)
      - Phoenix Suns, 1978-1991, 2 folders (Box CL101)
      - Pittsburgh Pirates (Box CL102)
        - General, 1976-1984 (Box CL102)
        - Cable, 1990 (Box CL102)
        - Radio, 1990 (Box CL102)
        - Television, 1990 (Box CL102)
      - Pittsburgh Steelers, 1986 Aug. 11 (Box CL102)
      - Portland Trailblazers, 1983-1986, 1990, 2 folders (Box CL102)
      - Sacramento Kings, 1991 (Box CL102)
      - St. Louis Blues, 1985 (Box CL102)
      - San Antonio Spurs, 1981-1985, 1989-1991, 3 folders (Box CL102)
      - San Diego Chargers
        - General, 1978-1985 (Box CL102)
        - Ordering letter and schedules, 1990 (Box CL102)
        - Radio, 1991 (Box CL102)
      - San Diego Clippers, 1977-1983 (Box CL102)
      - San Diego Padres
        - General, 1978-1987 (Box CL102)
        - Pay-view, 1990 (Box CL102)
      - San Francisco 49ers
        - General, 1978-1985, 1990, 2 folders (Box CL102)
        - 49ers/Raiders pre-season game, 1990 (Box CL102)
        - Hispanic, 1989 (Box CL102)
      - San Francisco Giants (Box CL103)
        - General, 1978-1987 (Box CL103)
        - Television, 1989 (Box CL103)
      - Seattle Mariners, 1978-1986 (Box CL103)
      - Seattle Sea Fair, 1989 June 14 (Box CL103)
      - Seattle Seahawks pre-season television, 1991 (Box CL103)
      - Seattle Supersonics, 1977-1986, 1990, 2 folders (Box CL103)
      - Senior Professional Baseball Association, 1990 (Box CL103)
      - Shreveport Captains--television, undated (Box CL103)
      - Tampa Bay Buccaneers
        - General, 1977-1986 (Box CL103)
        - Pre-season, 1990 (Box CL103)
        - Radio, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box CL103)
      - Tenth Frame, 1989 (Box CL103)
      - Texas Rangers, 1981-1985, 1990, 2 folders (Box CL103)
      - Twin Tier Bowling Challenge, 1989 Nov. (Box CL103)
      - United States Football League (USFL), 1983-1985 (Box CL103)
      - U.S. Open Highlights, 1989 June 5 (Box CL103)
      - Utah Jazz, 1976-1979, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box CL103)
      - Washington Bullets, 1979-1985, 1989-1991, 2 folders (Box CL103)
      - Washington Redskins (Box CL104)
        - General, 1977-1985 (Box CL104)
        - Joe Gibbs Show, 1989 May 26 (Box CL104)
        - Pre-season football, 1990 (Box CL104)
        - Radio, 1991 (Box CL104)
        - Television, 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box CL104)
        - Washington Redskins Anthology, 1991 June 5 (Box CL104)
        - Washington Redskins Magazine, 1989-1990 (Box CL104)
      - Miscellaneous professional sports proposals, 1990 (Box CL104)
    - Sketches and artwork
      - Produced by Backer Spielvogel Bates, 1970-1973 (Box CL105-CL107)
      - Produced by McCann-Erickson, 1975 (Box CL108-CL109)
    - Storyboards, 1989 and undated (Box CL110-CL112)
  - Murata Electronics
    - Proofs, 1997-1999 (Box CL113)
  - National Geographic
    - Print advertisements, 2001 (Box CL113)
  - Opensite
    - Proofs, 2000 (Box CL113)
  - Paddington Corp.
    - General (Box CL114)
      - Contact reports, 1980 (Box CL114)
      - Expense vouchers 1983-1985, 3 folders (Box CL114)
      - Invoices, 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box CL114)
      - Picon, Mindy, chronological files, 1984 Jan.-June, 2 folders (Box CL114)
      - Project Delta, 1982 Aug.-1983 (Box CL114)
      - Rosenthal, Larry, chronological files, 1982 Jan.-1984 Feb., Folder 1 of 13 (Box CL114)
      - Rosenthal, Larry, chronological files, 1982 Jan.-1984 Feb. (continued), Folders 2-10 of 13 (Box CL115)
      - Rosenthal, Larry, chronological files, 1982 Jan.-1984 Feb. (continued), Folders 11-13 of 13 (Box CL116)
      - Rowland, Michael, chronological files, 1982 Apr.-1983 Dec., Folders 1-5 of 11 (Box CL116)
      - Rowland, Michael, chronological files, 1982 Apr.-1983 Dec. (continued), Folders 6-11 of 11 (Box CL117)
      - Rums of Puerto Rico, advertising study, 1973 Aug. (Box CL117)